expertagent.co.uk 2018-11-11

# Privacy & Cookies - Expert Agent

### Cookie Policy

Websky Limited (“Expert Agent”, “we” or “us”) uses cookies and other similar technologies in the operation of this website.

A cookie is a piece of information that a website puts on your computer so it can remember something about you or your device at a later date. We use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website (including when you browse other third party websites). This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse this website. We also use cookies and similar technologies to show you more personalised advertising, including adverts on other websites. By using our website, you agree to our use of cookies.

This policy explains what cookies, including third party cookies, we use on our website, and how you can refuse or withdraw your consent to cookies. You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.eu.

The cookies on our website are either set by us or by third party partners and fall into the following categories:

### 1\. First Party Session Management

These are typically required by us to make sure you can move freely from one page to another and so you can access and use certain services within the site. Normally these cookies only last while your browser is open and are deleted when it is closed. Some may need to remain for longer than the duration of your visit (session) or longer.

**Cookie name** | **Description** | **Duration**  
---|---|---  
CONSENT | Recognises whether a user has accepted cookies when browsing our website | 2 years  
  
### 2\. Performance

We want to ensure we provide a good experience. These cookies (which are set by third parties providing services to us) allow us to monitor how visitors use our website. These cookies provide us with anonymous statistics on how many people visit the website, where they have come from and the pages they visit so that we can continue to develop and improve the website and our services. They also help us understand the effectiveness of our advertising.

### 3\. Functionality

These cookies allow you to set and store preferences for the website, such as when you are offered the option to customise elements of the layout or content of the website. These cookies may also help us to monitor, debug and optimise the performance of the website.

**Third party** | **Description**  
---|---  
AddThis | Collects information about your visit to our website for targeted advertising<http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out>  
Google Analytics | Collects statistical information about how you use the site so that we can improve the site<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
Wistia | Hosts video content on our website<https://wistia.com/privacy>  
Twitter | Social media integration<https://twitter.com/en/privacy>  
YouTube | Hosts video content on our website[https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines&gl=GB](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines&gl=GB)  
  
### Refusing or withdrawing your consent to the use of cookies

You may refuse to accept cookies by altering the settings on your internet browser. For more information about how to do this, look at your browser ‘help’ section or visit www.allaboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.eu.

Please note that if you adjust your internet browser settings to refuse the setting of cookies, you may not be able to access or use fully certain parts or functionality of our website.

### Updates to this policy

So that we can offer you the best possible online experience, new services using cookies may be added to our website from time to time. We aim to keep the cookies information provided here as accurate as possible and use all reasonable efforts to regularly review and update the details. When we update these details, we will post changes on this page so please check back frequently.

**Last updated: 23 May 2018**

### Expert Agent Privacy Policy

Websky Limited (“Expert Agent”, “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy explains how we use any personal information that you provide to us through our website. Please read it carefully. We may change this policy. We will post any changes on this page, so please check back frequently.

For the purposes of data protection law, the controller is Websky Limited of The Cooperage, 5 Copper Row, London SE1 2LH. Expert Agent is part of the ZPG Limited group of companies, comprising ZPG Limited and its subsidiaries (the “ZPG Companies”).

### Information we collect from you

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information you provide to us

You may provide us with information in several ways, including by filling in forms on our website or by corresponding with us by phone, email and live chat. This includes information you provide when you buy any of our products or services, enter a competition, promotion or survey, provide feedback or report a problem with our website.

This information may include your name, address, email address, phone number, payment details and any other information you provide to us.

  * Information we collect about you

When you use our website, we automatically collect information about your device, including your IP address, information about your visit (including how you got to our websites) and how you use our services. We may combine this information with other information you have provided to us or which we have received from other sources.

  * Information we receive from other sources

If you use any of the other websites or services provided by the ZPG Companies, we may receive information about you or your device in relation to that use, including your IP address, information about your visits how you use the services of the ZPG Companies.

We work closely with third parties (for example, business partners, advertising networks, analytics providers and search information providers) and may receive information about you from them. This could include socio-demographic information and information about your likely interests based on your previous web browsing and purchases. We may combine this information with other information you have provided to us or which we collected about you.

### How we use your personal information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * Providing our services to you and fulfilling your requests

o Providing you with the information, products and services you request from us or another ZPG Company.

o Completing any transaction you are undertaking with us or another ZPG Company.

o Administering promotions or competitions that you enter with us or another ZPG Company.

o Allowing you to participate in our interactive features when you choose to do so.

  * Marketing and advertising

o Providing you and others with information about goods and services that we, other ZPG Companies and selected third parties offer that may interest you or them, which may be based on inferences about your or their likely interests based on your activity on websites operated by ZPG Companies or third parties.

o Customising or enhancing your experience of our services, which may use inferences about your likely interests based on your activity on websites operated by ZPG Companies or third parties.

o Delivering relevant advertising to you on websites operated by ZPG Companies or third parties or in direct communications from us, which may use inferences about your likely interests based on your activity on websites operated by ZPG Companies or third parties.

o Measuring and understanding the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others.

  * Service improvement and account management

o Ensuring that our content is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device.

o Administering our websites and apps and for internal business administration (for example, troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes).

o Protecting our interests and those of third parties and as part of our efforts to keep our services safe and secure.

o Managing and operating your account with us.

### Legal basis for processing

Our legal basis for processing your personal information for the purposes described above will typically be one of the following:

  * Contract

It is necessary for us to process your personal information to perform a contract to which you are a party, or to take steps at your request prior to you entering into a contract.

  * Consent

You have consented to us using your personal information for this purpose (for example, when you create an account with us, agree to receive marketing emails from us or create an alert). You can withdraw your consent at any time by deleting the information from your account or updating your marketing preferences.

  * Legitimate interests

It is in our legitimate interests to use your personal information to operate, improve and promote our services (for example, when we customise your experience of our services or use your information for analytics purposes) and to protect our business. Sometimes, we may process your personal information when it is in the legitimate interests of another company, such as another ZPG Company.

  * Legal obligations

It is necessary for us to use your personal information for us or another ZPG Company to comply with a legal obligation.

### Sharing your personal information

We share IT infrastructure with other ZPG Companies, and so we may share your personal information with those ZPG Companies to help store your data efficiently and securely. Other ZPG Companies may access your personal information to help provide you with services that you request from those ZPG Companies (for example, to help you manage your home) and to provide you with relevant recommendations of other ZPG services and products. These recommendations may use inferences about your interests based on your activity on our websites and apps and on other websites and apps operated by other ZPG Companies.

We may also share your personal information with third parties in the following circumstances:

  * Our service providers: to help us run our business and perform services you request

We may provide your personal information to our business partners, suppliers and subcontractors who provide services to us or where necessary to perform a service that you have requested.

  * Advertisers and advertising networks: to serve relevant adverts to you and others

We may provide your personal information to our partner advertisers and advertising networks that require that information to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others.

  * Analytics and search engine providers: to help us improve our services

We may provide information about your visit to analytics and search engine providers to help us improve and optimise our services. We generally only share this information in a form that does not directly identify you.  
We may also share your personal information with third parties for the following reasons:

  * If we sell or buy any business or assets

If we sell or buy any business or assets, we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of that business or those assets, along with its professional advisers. If Expert Agent (or substantially all of its assets) is acquired, personal information held by it about its users will be one of the transferred assets.

  * To obtain professional advice

We may disclose your personal information to obtain professional advice (for example, from lawyers or financial advisors).

  * To comply with a legal obligation

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in response to a request from law enforcement or another regulatory authority. We may disclose your personal information to enforce our agreements with you or to protect the rights, property or safety of Expert Agent, its users or others. This includes sharing personal information with other organisations for fraud prevention purposes.

### Storing your personal information

We may transfer, store or process your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). The laws in some countries may not provide as much legal protection for your personal information as in the EEA.

By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Where we use service providers outside the EEA, we rely on approved data transfer mechanisms (for example, the EU Standard Contractual Clauses and the EU-US Privacy Shield) to ensure that your personal information is adequately safeguarded in the recipient country.

Where you have a password to enable you to access some parts of our websites or apps, you are responsible for keeping that password confidential. You must not share your password with anyone.  
Unfortunately, transmission of information over the internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee its security and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

We keep your personal information for as long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is processed. These periods vary depending on the nature of the information and your interactions with us.

### Cookies

We use cookies and other similar technologies to distinguish you from other users of our websites and apps (including when you browse third party websites). This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you use our services (for example, to remember your login details and improve our services). We also use cookies and similar technologies to show you more personalised advertising, including Expert Agent ads on other websites. You may adjust the settings on your browser to refuse cookies but some of our services may not work if you do so. For detailed information on the cookies we use and why we use them, please read our Cookie Policy (see above).

### Opting out of collection of information by third party advertisers

Our third party advertisers and advertising network providers (“Ad Providers”) may provide you with ads on our websites and apps or on other websites. To make those ads more relevant and help measure their effectiveness, the Ad Providers may use cookies and similar technologies. They record your activity (including pages visited) and estimate what information interests you most. They use this information in accordance with their own privacy policies. For a link to each of those policies and for information about how to opt out, please read our Cookie Policy (above).

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. You can do this at any time by updating your email preferences in your Expert Agent account or by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any marketing email we send you.

Data protection law gives you the right to access your personal information, to object to the use of your personal information for certain purposes, and the right to erase, restrict or receive a machine-readable copy of your personal information. You can access, update and delete the information Expert Agent holds about you by emailing privacy@zpg.co.uk or by contacting us using the address below.  
We will handle your request in accordance with the law. This means there may be legal reasons why we cannot fulfil all requests.

### Links to third party websites

Our websites and apps may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy does not apply to those other websites and we do not accept liability for the content of any other website. Please check the privacy policy of any other website before submitting any personal information to it.

### Contact us

If you have questions about this privacy policy or the way in which Expert Agent processes your personal information, you can contact us using the details below:

Post: Data Protection Manger, Websky Limited, The Cooperage, 5 Copper Row, London SE1 2LH

**Email** : privacy@zpg.co.uk

We hope that we will be able to resolve any questions or concerns you have. However, you may at any time raise your concern with the UK Information Commissioner at:  
Post: Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF

**Last updated: 23 May 2018**
